infoniac.com 2014-06-30

# InfoNIAC - Latest Inventions

InfoNIAC is aware of the fact that you care about the use of your personal information and how this information is shared, and our team takes your privacy seriously. It is important that you read and understand our privacy policy. By visiting InfoNIAC you accept the information stipulated in this Privacy Policy. 

This privacy policy cannot be applied to the third parties that InfoNIAC does not own or manage, or to individuals that do not work at InfoNIAC. 

### Collecting Personal Information

The main goal of our community, regarding personal information gathering, is to provide its users with a friendly and efficient experience. InfoNIAC team only processes personal data with the purpose for which the information has been gathered or authorized by you. The types of information collected from users include:

  1.  _ **Information Provided by Users:**_  
InfoNIAC team receives and stores all information you provide on our website or in any other way. You have the option not to provide certain information. Personal information is needed for registration, so to be able to use our services, including commenting and submitting new content to the website. When registering, you should also provide your email (see our Privacy Policy).  

  2. _**Other Information:**_  

    * When you interact with InfoNIAC we receive and store specific types of information. We automatically collect and record certain information on traffic, including IP addresses. InfoNIAC only uses this data for to purpose of diagnosing certain problems and site administration. 
    * InfoNIAC allows other users to look through submitted or commented news. 
    * InfoNIAC promises the confidentiality of all passwords and settings of its users.

Information provided by you represents an integral part of our job. InfoNIAC team neither gives away, rents nor sells your personal data to anyone. 

Your account information on our site is protected by password. You have to log out when you have finished using our services. 

### Information Access 

Users can access personal information on their page on InfoNIAC and edit or delete what they consider to be inaccurate. 

### Your Choices

  * You may not to disclose your personal information. 
  * You can add or update your information. 
  * You can end using our services. 

InfoNIAC reserves the right to change the current Privacy Policy at its sole discretion. In case InfoNIAC team makes any changes in its Privacy Policy, all changes will be posted on the site's home page, so you could always be aware.
